New York City protects landmarks and
there's a whole list of them with very
obvious ones the Statue of Liberty the
Empire State Building even the entirety
of Central Park but located directly on
the East River in Queens is a bit of an
odd Landmark this Pepsi Cola sign the
sign was originally constructed in 1940
and was made for the roof of a Pepsi
Bottling plant here where it was
directly opposite of the United Nations
building as the most stereotypical
reminder to diplomats which country they
are currently in even though the sign
today is a reconstruction built in 1994
the sign has been around for long enough
that the city deemed it worth protecting
in 2016 perhaps more rightfully than
designed in the noo District of Lowa
Manhattan this building is also a New
York City landmark and it houses a
cinema which me and a couple of my
Creator friends have rented and you can
join us each one of us will show one of
their videos on the big screen and we
will be there for a chat afterwards
check the comments below to get tickets